{
    "subject": "resource/David_Parks_(politician)",
    "predicate": "property/party",
    "object": "Republican Party",
    "human_readable": "David Parks (politician) was a member of the Republican Party.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9852103590965271,
            "question": "Was David Parks a Republican politician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9296638369560242,
            "question": "Was David Parks a member of the Democratic Party?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9202219247817993,
            "question": "Was David Parks a member of any political parties?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9076351523399353,
            "question": "Did David Parks identify as a Republican?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8944782018661499,
            "question": "To which political party did David Parks belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.866251528263092,
            "question": "What political party was David Parks affiliated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8628749847412109,
            "question": "In what political party did David Parks serve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8052669763565063,
            "question": "What was the political stance of David Parks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7826067805290222,
            "question": "What was David Parks's political affiliation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7006897926330566,
            "question": "With which political party did David Parks align himself?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=David Parks (politician) was a member of the Republican Party.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5456_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was David Parks's political affiliation?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5456_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the political stance of David Parks?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5456_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what political party did David Parks serve?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5456_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5456_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5456_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5456_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5456_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5456_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5456_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5456_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5456_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5456_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5456_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not mention David Parks being associated with the Republican Party. Instead, they indicate that he is a Democrat. For instance, the document at path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5456/re-ranker-msmarco/102.txt` mentions \"Senator David Parks (D)\", where (D) typically stands for Democratic Party in U.S. politics."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}